A Guide to the Papers of Richard B. O'Keeffe ca.1973-2003>
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Richard B. O'Keeffe ca. 1973-2002
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10757-p
This collection consists of the papers of Richard B. O 'Keeffe, former Library Bibliographer, George Mason University, Fairfax, Virginia, ca. 540 items (11 Hollinger boxes, 4.5 linear feet).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
These papers were given to the University of Virginia Library by Richard B. O'Keeffe, Arlington, Virginia on January 22, 2002.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the papers of Richard B. O 'Keeffe, former Library Bibliographer, George Mason University, Fairfax, Virginia, ca. 540 items (11 Hollinger boxes, 4.5 linear feet), ca. 1973-2002, chiefly 103 volumes of bound journals, typescript copies of thirteen journals removed from loose leaf binders, seventeen computer diskettes (volumes 118-148 of his journal covering 1989 October 17 through 1993 December 31), and three other bound volumes containing notes, etc.
Also present are typescript copies of journal indexes, correspondence and notes about bibliographies, data files, notes about George Mason University theses, indexes to WhoSez compilations, and miscellaneous notes and references to Robert Hanssen.
Contents List
- Series I: Journals and Journal Indexes
  - Journals, Volumes 1-16 1974-1977 Jan., 16 volumes (Box 1)
  - Journals, Volumes 17-30 1977 Jan.-1978 Oct., 14 volumes (Box 2)
  - Journals, Volumes 31-46 1978 Oct.-1980 Nov., 16 volumes (Box 3)
  - Journals, Volumes 47-62 1980 Nov.-1982 Aug., 16 volumes (Box 4)
  - Journals, Volumes 63-75 1982 Aug.-1984 Apr., 13 volumes (Box 5)
  - Journal, Volume 76 1984 Jan.-Feb., Typescript (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Journal, Volume 77 1984 Mar.-Apr. 14, Typescript (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Journal, Volume 78 1984 Apr. 15-May 28, Typescript (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Journal, Volume 79 1984 May 29-Jul. 18, Typescript (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Journal, Volume 80 1984 Jul. 19-Sep. 14, Typescript (Box 7)
  - Journal, Volume 81 1984 Sep. 15-Oct. 18, Typescript (Box 7)
  - Journal, Volume 82 1984 Oct. 19-Nov. 21, Typescript (Box 7)
  - Journal, Volume 83 1984 Nov. 22-Dec. 18, Typescript (Box 7)
  - Journal, Volume 84 1984 Dec. 19-1985 Jan. 15, Typescript (Box 7)
  - Journal, Volume 85 1985 Jan. 15-Feb. 9, Typescript (Box 7)
  - Journal, Volume 86 1985 Feb. 10-Mar. 3, Typescript (Box 7)
  - Journal, Volume 87 1985 Mar. 3-30, Typescript (Box 7)
  - Journal, Volume 89 1985 Apr. 26-May 24, Typescript (Box 7)
  - Journals, Volumes 90-103 1985 May 25-1987 Jun., 14 volumes (Box 8)
  - Journals, Volumes 104-117 1987 Jun.-1989 Oct., 14 volumes (Box 9)
  - Journal Volume 134 1991 Dec., Typescript (Box 10)
  - Journal Volume January 1995 1995 Jan.-Feb. (Box 10)
  - Journal Indexes Volumes 91-117 1985 Jul.-1989 Oct., Typescript (4 folders) (Box 10)
- Series II: Miscellaneous Papers
  - Correspondence and Notes re Bibliographies ca. 1990-1992, n.d., 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Data Files of O'Keeffe and Others ca. 1976-1999, 1 of 3 folders (Box 10)
  - Data Files of O'Keeffe and Others ca. 1976-1999, 2 of 3 folders (Box 11)
  - George Mason University Theses 1989 May 30 (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous Notes 1991-1994, n.d. (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous Notes re Robert Hanssen ca. 1980-2001, n.d., 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous Volumes 1973, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Notes 1996 Fall (Box 11)
  - Who Sez Alphabets A Decennial Compilation 1974-1983 1989 Apr. 24 (Box 11)
  - Who Sez Miscellaneous Indexes 1977-1996 (Box 11)